William Kelly Simpson Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Publications, Series IX
  - Nubian Salvage Campaign, Articles Naming Yale and William K. Simpson., 037318
  - Nubian Salvage Campaign, General Articles., 037319
  - Other Publications by Bruce Trigger, Reprints., 037320
  - Publications of the Pennsylvania-Yale Expedition to Egypt., 037321
  - Draft and Notes for "The Pennsylvania-Yale Expedition to Egypt, Preliminary Report for 1963: Toshka and Arminna (Nubia)," William Kelly Simpson, JARCE, Vol. III, 1964., 037339
  - Draft and Notes for "Toshka-Arminna 1962, The Pennsylvania-Yale Archaeological Expedition to Nubia," William Kelly Simpson, Fouilles en Nubie (1961 - 1963), Cairo 1967., 037340
  - Notes on Unpublished Manuscript titled "Arminna West: The Late Nubian Necropolis and Meroitic Buildings Excavated 1963 (Vol. 7)., 037341
  - Notes, Drawings and Photos Related to Publication of Volume 1: Hekanefer and the Dynastic Material from Toshka and Arminna, William Kelly Simpson., 037342
  - Notes, Drawings and Photos Related to Publication of Volume 2: The Late Nubian Settlement at Arminna West, Bruce G. Trigger., 037343
  - Notes, Drawings and Photos Related to Publication of Volume 3: The Classic Christian Townsite at Arminna West, Kent R. Weeks., 037344
  - Notes, Drawings and Photos Related to Publication of Volume 4: The Meroitic Funerary Inscriptions from Arminna West, Bruce G. Trigger., 037345
  - Pre-publication Figures (Over-sized), William K Simpson, Expedition, Vol. 4. No. 2, Winter 1962. Note that many of these figures are the same as in the Hekanefer publication (Vol. 1 of Publications of the Penn-Yale Expedition to Egypt/Nubia). Stored in same box as Antar.037352-037355., 037352
  - Pre-publication Figures (Over-sized), William K Simpson, Expedition, Vol. 4, No. 4, Summer 1962. Stored in same box as Antar.037352-037355., 037353
  - Pre-publication Figures and Plates (Over-sized), Volume 1: Hekanefer and the Dynastic Material from Toshka and Arminna, William K Simpson. For additional plates, also see ANTAR.037352. Stored in same box as Antar.037352-037355., 037354
  - Pre-publication Text and Plates (Over-sized), Volume 3: The Classic Christian Townsite at Arminna West, Kent R. Weeks. Note: Not scanned due to uncut pages. Refer to published work ANTAR.037348. Stored in same box as Antar.037352-037355., 037355
  - Pre-publication Plates (Over-sized), Volume 2: The Late Nubian Settlement at Arminna West, Bruce G. Trigger., 037356
  - Pre-Publication Plates Related to Publication of Volume 6: Inscribed Material from the Pennsylvania-Yale Excavations at Abydos, William Kelley Simpson., 041858
  - Pre-Publication Plates. Pahe 1 and 2 from an unknown publication. Page 3 from Rudolf Anthes, 1965, "Mit Rahineh 1956", plate 15. Page 5 from Anthes 1965, plate 21. Page 7 from Anthes 1965, plate 55., 041859
- Miscellaneous, Series X
  - Miscellaneous Teaching Materials, William Kelly Simpson., 037358
  - Student Papers and Research Regarding Toshka-Arminna., 037359
  - Documentation Found with Teaching Collection Slides., 040701
  - Objects from the William Kelly Simpson Archive., 040702
  - Miscellaneous Mid-sized Illustrations., 041775
  - Miscellaneous Mid-sized Materials from the Penn-Yale Expedition., 041776
  - William Kelly Simpson's Research Bibliography; 5 boxes of index cards organized alphabetically by author., 041833
- Oversize, Series XI
  - Arminna East. Oversize Flat Illustrations and Rubbings., 041570
  - Arminna East. Oversize Rolled Illustrations., 041763
  - Arminna West. Oversize Flat Illustrations., 041569
  - Arminna West. Oversize Rolled Illustrations., 041762
  - Toshka East. Oversize Flat Illustrations and Rubbings., 041161
  - Toshka West. Oversize Flat Illustrations and Rubbings., 041568
  - Toshka East, Oversize Flat Maps., 041147
  - Toshka West, Oversize Flat Maps., 041148
  - Arminna East, Oversize Flat Maps., 041149
  - Arminna West, Oversize Flat Maps., 041150
  - Miscellaneous Oversize Flat Maps., 041151
  - Miscellanous Flat Oversize Illustrations, Charts and Texts., 041721
  - Miscellanous Rolled Oversize Illustrations., 041749
  - Toshka West, Oversize Rolled Maps., 041750
  - Toshka East, Oversize Rolled Illustrations., 041751
  - Arminna West, Oversize Rolled Maps., 041752
  - Miscellaneous Oversize Rolled Maps., 041753